[
  {
    "question": "You should have already listened to the Note-Taking Practice 1 lecture. Use your notes to answer the questions. What is the topic of the lecture?",
    "answers": ["Things that make lectures difficult to understand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this lecture about a study or about the speaker's own ideas?",
    "answers": ["a study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the speaker mention “the Freshman 15”?",
    "answers": ["To give a specific example of what lecture complexity is"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, what does the word “redundancy” mean?",
    "answers": ["Saying the same word or concept more than once"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following in NOT an example of how a speaker “delivers” a lecture?",
    "answers": ["How well the lecture is organized"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is mentioned as a strategy for effective listening in class?",
    "answers": [
      "Reviewing notes after class.",
      "Reading about the topic before class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker gave the following example: “reviewing the lecture notes after class.” What idea does this example support?",
    "answers": ["Strategies to help understand lectures"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 2 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. According to the lecture, what are “learning styles”?",
    "answers": [
      "Learning styles are the different ways that people learn best."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the speaker want to focus on the kinesthetic learning style?",
    "answers": ["Because not very people know much about it"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the speaker’s explanation of how learners learn, which of the following would NOT be a good example of how kinesthetic learners learn best?",
    "answers": [
      "Going to a live theater production",
      "Listening to your classmates summarize the lesson in a study group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of the following characteristics of kinesthetic learners, which did the speaker mention first?",
    "answers": ["Very coordinated"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker mentioned “flashcards” as an example for what idea?",
    "answers": ["Study tools you can manipulate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following occupations do you think would NOT be best for a kinesthetic learner?",
    "answers": ["novelist", "Secretary"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The language cue “because” is used in the lecture to explain why all the topics in the outline may not be taught in the course. Select the TWO reasons that were given.",
    "answers": [
      "That material is sometimes taught in two semesters.",
      "There will not be enough time."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "“Nevertheless” shows contrast; it shows something that is the opposite of what is being discussed. Why did the professor use the language cue “nevertheless” in the phrase “nevertheless there are some very important aspects of it like black holes . . . “ ?",
    "answers": [
      "Black holes are an application of the General Relativity theory and the phrase preceding “nevertheless” states that there will not be much time to discuss possible applications."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "See how well you can determine meaning of an actual professor giving an introduction to Einstein’s General Relativity and Gravitation. The lecture is 4 minutes 39 seconds long. First, watch the entire video, then answer the following questions. General Relativity and Gravitation Lecture Play Video What phrase did the professor use to give the topic of the class?",
    "answers": ["“This class is about . . . .”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following topics will be presented first in the class?",
    "answers": ["the foundations of General Relativity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The professor says, “in a number of occasions I will use the famous phrase ‘it can be shown’.” When will he say “it can be shown”?",
    "answers": [
      "He will use this phrase when he doesn’t have time to show the proof."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The language cues are in bold and underlined in the following excerpt of the lecture. Which TWO language cues signal a restatement of something that was already explained? In order to understand the theory, we need some mathematics, and it turns out that general relativity requires some understanding of tensor calculus. That is, in order to understand the foundation of Einstein’s theory and why it is in fact unique, we need to understand the mathematics that comes with it, which is not trivial but nevertheless is an essential part of it. In other words, you cannot discuss general relativity without tensor calculus and differential geometry",
    "answers": ["in other words", "that is"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following topics will be presented last in the class?",
    "answers": ["applications of General Relativity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What language cue informs us that Einstein did not immediately get together with Marcel Grossman?",
    "answers": ["eventually"]
  },

  {
    "question": "What language cue was used to state that the aim of the class was to focus on fundamental issues and not practical applications of the theory?",
    "answers": ["rather not"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 3 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. Which of the following topics does Dave NOT lecture on?",
    "answers": ["SAT (undergraduate entrance exam)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The Research Paragraph should be included at the end of the Statement of Purpose.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of the following topics to investigate, which did the speaker mention first?",
    "answers": ["Mission Statement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The Research Paragraph should include information about the school’s Mission Statement, Curriculum, Faculty, and Facilities.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what order did the speaker mention the following topics?",
    "answers": ["Mission Statement, Curriculum, Faculty, Facilities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following examples of facilities at a university should not be mentioned in the Research Paragraph?",
    "answers": ["Libraries"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The speaker did not use any language cues.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 4 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. What are the benefits of learning how to manage time well?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of the following concepts that were discussed in the talk, which was mentioned last?",
    "answers": ["Be realistic and kind to yourself."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True orFalse? When considering what is most important to you, you should think about solutions to the everyday expectations that make you worry and put these first into your calendar.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the talk, the speaker gives the following examples: “Well, I have this test tomorrow,\" or \"I have this bill that is due on Friday.” Which of the five time management concepts was he talking about when he gave these examples?",
    "answers": ["Identify what is most important to you."]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, what is the main reason that people give up on the schedule that they make for themselves?",
    "answers": [
      "They try to fit in too much into their schedule and then become frustrated when they cannot accomplish it all."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some ways that you can “be realistic and kind to yourself” as you manage your time?",
    "answers": ["All of the above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language cues did the speaker use?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement do you think the speaker would probably agree with?",
    "answers": [
      "Planning in social time with friends and family should be on the “most important” list.",
      "The Statement of Purpose needs to be written in a very confident, well organized, intentional manner.",
      "People learn best in different ways.",
      "It is important for you to know how you learn best."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 4 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. Who would benefit from watching this video about Time Management?",
    "answers": ["Everyone . . . including those listed above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of the following concepts that were discussed in the talk, which was mentioned first?",
    "answers": ["Know when you work best."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Many people say, “I’d love to do this, but I don’t have time for it” or “I wish I would do this right, but I don’t have time.” According to the speaker, how can this be avoided?",
    "answers": [
      "Figure out what you love and what is most important and plan those things first into your schedule."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the the lecture, which statement do you think the speaker would probably agree with?",
    "answers": [
      "The main aim of managing time well is to keep a person happy, not stressed, and still productive."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the talk, the speaker gives the following examples: “ . . . it could be house cleaning. If you are in an office environment, it could be reading or reviewing emails. ” Which of the five time management concepts was he talking about when he gave these examples?",
    "answers": ["Schedule mindless maintenance during “lazy” hours."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good practices for taking lecture notes? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Make sure you understand any assignments, and ask the teacher if you don't understand.",
      "Pay attention to language, visual, and verbal cues that help you identify key points.",
      "Write down what the teacher writes on the board or highlights in a PowerPoint.",
      "Compare notes with classmates after class to make sure they are accurate.",
      "Review the notes from the previous lecture while you wait for class to begin.",
      "Compare notes with classmates to make sure they are accurate.",
      "Write down what the teacher writes on the board or highlights in a Powerpoint.",
      "Develop a personal note-taking system and use a notebook."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you have a good memory, you don't have to take notes during a lecture.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Lecturers in universities may have many different speaking styles.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When you take notes, you should try to write down main ideas and details.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It's fine not to listen during a lecture because you can always listen to a recording later.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following should you write in the space on the left when taking Cornell notes? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "questions you have",
      "important phrases",
      "main idea",
      "study questions",
      "key vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When should you fill in the section on the right-side of the page when using a Cornell Notes template?",
    "answers": ["during the lecture"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good practices for taking notes during the lecture when using the Cornell Notes method? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "use note-taking shortcuts",
      "skip lines on the page",
      "indent the supporting details under each main point",
      "use lots of space on the page"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk. Take thorough notes using one of the templates you've been given. Then answer all of the questions that follow. Play Video What does the speaker think would make the audience relax as he begins his talk?",
    "answers": ["Telling the audience how he was going to present his ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the speaker want to show about a person with ADD when he shows this drawing?",
    "answers": ["They are very sensitive to everything that is around them."]
  },
  {
    "question": "As the speaker hugged people in his costume, he learned something amazing: “that all of us want to be loved.” How did he emphasize this point? (Choose two answers.)",
    "answers": [
      "Pausing for for 3 seconds before he shared what he realized.",
      "Saying “I learned something amazing”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Since groups realized how important it is to “make people love you”, everyone is constantly broadcasting. Which of the following examples of how information is being broadcasted were NOT mentioned?",
    "answers": ["YouTube"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The speaker thinks social media is generally being used in a positive way.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main point of the talk?",
    "answers": ["Be genuine and just be who you are with others"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s see how effective the notes that you took in the Listening Strategies lecture are. See if they can help you answer the following questions. If not, listen to that lecture again. How is the information organized in the lecture?",
    "answers": [
      "In the order of time (chronologically) when things happen first, second, and third"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many main things were mentioned that listeners need to do DURING the lecture?",
    "answers": ["2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important to emphasize key vocabulary and information in your notes. Which of the following ways of emphasizing information were mentioned in the lecture?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Language cues show you how to pronounce a word.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of information do language cues signal? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "a generalization",
      "organization of the lecture",
      "contrast of ideas",
      "topic",
      "the meaning of the lecture",
      "the speaker's opinion",
      "important information",
      "an explanation of a word or concept"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of language cues? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "That means...",
      "This class is about...",
      "In order to...",
      "Let's move on to...",
      "Most importantly..."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk titled “Embrace Your Disobedience” by Diego Rosso. Take thorough notes using one of the templates you've been given. Then answer the questions that follow. Lecture Clip Play Video How did the speaker get the audience to focus on his topic at the beginning of his presentation? (Read all the answer choices before you choose an answer.)",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the speaker tell the story about the student who visited him in his office? (It starts at 7:40.)",
    "answers": ["To show how a professor can learn from a student."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language cue(s) were used? (Read all the choices before you decide, especially the last one.) (Note: You normally wouldn't put these words in your notes, but you should be paying attention to them in this class to help you follow the organization of the lectures.)",
    "answers": ["All of the above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the last bit of the talk, starting at 10:40 and answer the question below. Short Clip Play Video What does the speaker mean?",
    "answers": [
      "The speaker will feel successful if his research about bubbles helps someone else to do something great, even if he is not remembered."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is one good place mentioned in the lecture to write down \"housekeeping\" items from the beginning of a lecture?",
    "answers": ["in a calendar"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? You should write down the hook of the lecture on the first page of your notes.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the lecture introduction do you need to pay closest attention to?",
    "answers": ["the important information"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The questions should guide you in observing important aspects of the introduction. The questions will aim to make sure that you have understood the important content that the professor is trying to communicate. Listen to the lecture clip, and choose the best and most specific answer to each question. Question 1 Clip Play Video How does the professor prefer to be addressed?",
    "answers": ["Julie"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 2 Clip Play Video When sending an email to the professor, what should the subject of the email include?",
    "answers": ["The name of the class: ESS 1", "ESS1"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 3 Clip Play Video Which of the following topics would you NOT expect to learn about in this class?",
    "answers": [
      "how to be safe during a natural disaster",
      "procedures during a natural disaster"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 4 Clip Play Video True or False? The professor will upload two different versions of her lecture slides for each lecture.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 5 Clip Play Video True or false? You should review your notes within one week of hearing the lecture.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 6 Clip Play Video Which kind of information from the introduction does this clip contain?",
    "answers": ["Housekeeping information"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 7 Clip Play Video What skill does the professor expect his students to develop in his physics course?",
    "answers": ["the ability to identify important information"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the video clip taken from a longer lecture called “The Distracted Mind,” given by Professor Gazzaley. Take notes on your own paper. Do your best to identify the main idea and details from the lecture segment and to write them in indented form as you learned to do in the Main Idea video lecture. Then answer the following questions. Lecture Clip Play Video True or false? The main idea of this lecture is about all the positive characteristics of the brain.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Professor Gazzaley named the three limitations in the beginning, but he presented them in a different order. What order did he PRESENT the three limitations?",
    "answers": ["attention, speed, working memory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he said, “and that is why some people say that phone numbers are only seven digits long.” Which limitation was he referring to?",
    "answers": ["working memory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he says that “the brain is a vast network and so information has to travel between many regions which in the brain is very far.” What limitation is he describing when he says this?",
    "answers": ["speed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he says that “You have a build up of processing lags.” What limitation is he describing when he says this?",
    "answers": ["speed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk titled “The Future of Water” by Bill Cooper. Take thorough notes on one of the templates you've been given. Do your best to identify the important information that you should put in your notes based on the video lesson you have just watched. Then answer the following questions. Lecture Clip (This will open in a new window.) 1. True or False. The following outline represents the structure of the lecture.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much of the world’s oxygen is produced from phytoplankton in the ocean?",
    "answers": ["50%"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of this talk?",
    "answers": [
      "To make people realize that there is not an unlimited amount of water and that the environment needs to be respected"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What statement do you think the speaker would probably NOT agree with?",
    "answers": ["There is nothing we can do to fix this water problem."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the video segment of Professor Loftus speaking about “The fiction of memory”. Take notes. Do your best to identify the important information that you should put in your notes based on the video lesson you have just watched. Then answer the following questions. Lecture Clip Play Video What does Dr. Loftus study?",
    "answers": [
      "When people remember untrue information",
      "When people remember things that never happened"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language cue do we use to identify the important information of what Dr. Loftus studies?",
    "answers": ["Parallel Structure"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to a project conducted in the United States, how many innocent people have been convicted of a crime they did not do?",
    "answers": ["300"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What verbal cues helps us identify the important information the number of people convicted due to a false memory? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Louder volume", "Higher pitch", "Spoken more slowly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Look at this transcript from part of the video you just watched. What words and concepts are repeated in order to emphasize the important point that people were wrongly convicted of crimes because witnesses remembered the facts that really didn’t happen? Select TWO. “In one project in the United States, information has been gathered on 300 innocent people, 300 defendants who were convicted of crimes they didn't do. They spent 10, 20, 30 years in prison for these crimes, and now DNA testing has proven that they are actually innocent. And when those cases have been analyzed, three quarters of them are due to faulty memory, faulty eyewitness memory.”",
    "answers": ["faulty", "innocent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Directly after Dr. Loftus says “Three quarters of them are due to faulty memory,” she says, “But why?” These two words signal that she will give a reason why innocent people have been put in jail due to faulty memories. What is the reason?",
    "answers": [
      "Because the jurors believe the everything the witnesses say is true."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When the word “hit” was emphasized, people recalled that cars were going faster and they reported that there was broken glass at the accident, even though in reality there wasn’t.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What phrase, or language cue, does Dr. Loftus use to signal the findings of the experiments that she described?",
    "answers": [" “ . . . what these studies are showing is that . . . “"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Video Clip Play Video What does the dark green line refer to?",
    "answers": ["Americans believe there is more crime."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 2 Video Clip Play Video What year was the survey given?",
    "answers": ["2011"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 3 Video Clip Play Video What are the two data sets comparing?",
    "answers": [
      "People’s perception of crime nationally versus crime in their neighborhood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Play Video Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 4 Video Clip Which chart/graph did the professor use?",
    "answers": ["line graph"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Video Clip Play Video What is the chart/graph in this video clip measuring?",
    "answers": ["What is the actual number of violent crime victims?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 2 Video Clip Play Video Think about the information you heard in the video clips in the previous activity, Analyzing Charts and Graphs Listening Practice 1, and compare them with the findings in this video clip. What can you conclude?",
    "answers": ["People’s perception of violent crime is worse than reality."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 3 Video Clip Play Video What is the chart/graph measuring?",
    "answers": [
      "The amount of property crime compared to violent crime in California"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 4 Video Clip Play Video The professor says, “We see a precipitous drop in property crime.” Which sentence below has the closest meaning?",
    "answers": ["We see a significant drop in property crime."]
  },
  {
    "question": "For questions 1-3, listen to the lecture clip below on psychology and take notes as you listen. Pay attention to the information in the charts or graphs. After you listen, use your notes to answer the following questions. Questions 1-3 Lecture Clip Play Video Prof. Steyvers mentions a study by Ebbinghuas. What was Ebbinghaus trying to study in the experiment?",
    "answers": [
      "whether there is a relationship between retention interval on memory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What graph/chart did the professor use?",
    "answers": ["line graph"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Ebbinghaus found that after about 10 hours, all memory was usually lost and relearning had to occur.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For question 4, listen to the lecture clip below on psychology and take notes as you listen. Pay attention to the information in the charts or graphs. After you listen, use your notes to answer the following questions. Question 4 Lecture Clip Play Video What is the suggested cause for a reminiscence bump?",
    "answers": ["both optimal brain function and primacy effect"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Diction involves the words that a person chooses to express their meaning.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following words convey a positive tone or stance? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["beneficial", "logical", "positive", "dynamic", "purposeful"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As you learned in the lecture, qualifiers and intensifiers communicate how certain a speaker is in a statement. Choose the correct order of words and phrases below to show how certain a speaker would be when using them. The first word should be the most certain, and the last word should be the least certain.",
    "answers": [
      "clearly evident, absolutely, definitely, without a doubt likely possible not likely, doubtful improbable inconceivable, no way, not possible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the lecture clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 1 Lecture Clip Play Video Which word could be used to describe the speaker’s stance/tone/attitude?",
    "answers": ["insistent", "urgent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the lecture clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 2 Lecture Clip Play Video Which word could be used to describe the speaker’s stance/tone/attitude?",
    "answers": ["disheartened", "disappointed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The speaker’s main point is easier to understand when you understand his or her stance and attitude.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip that belongs with each question. Then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video The view held by ancient people that the Earth is fixed and the stars and planets are moving around the Earth is an example of:",
    "answers": ["An inductive inference"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 2 Clip Play Video The statement that a light year is a measurement of distance, not of time, is true by:",
    "answers": ["Definition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 3 Clip Play Video This argument was used in the lecture: Premise 1: Only elementary particles can exist in an extremely dense environment. Premise 2: The universe was infinitely dense when it was first born in the Big Bang. Conclusion: Therefore, only elementary particles existed when the universe was first born in the Big Bang. This deductive argument is:",
    "answers": ["Valid"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip that belongs with each question. Then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video The idea that a schema can be based on atypical (non-typical) information is false by:",
    "answers": ["Definition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 2 Clip Play Video This is an argument that was in the clip. Premise 1: Confidence and accuracy are not always positively correlated. Premise 2: For eyewitness accounts to be right, confidence and accuracy must be positively correlated. Conclusion: Therefore, eyewitness accounts are not always right. This conclusion follows the premises by:",
    "answers": ["Deductive inference"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 3 Clip Play Video A unbiased lineup of six individuals would have a probability of 1/6 (16.7%) for each individual. It is necessarily true that a 46% probability of choosing one of the individuals shows bias due to:",
    "answers": ["Mathematical necessity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three parts of a good presentation?",
    "answers": ["introduction, body, and conclusion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This photo is an example of which mode of persuasion?",
    "answers": ["pathos"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If the audience doesn’t feel that you are a trustworthy expert with thorough knowledge of your subject matter, what have you lost?",
    "answers": ["ethos"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follow. Question 4 Clip (This will open in a new window.) Play Video What information was NOT provided?",
    "answers": ["The reasons why there are several types of shoppers."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the questions that follow. Question 5 Clip (This will open in a new window.) Play Video Does this presenter use the three parts of an introduction mentioned in this week's lectures?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Throughout the presentation, the speaker seemed to present information __________.",
    "answers": ["objectively (neutrally)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker does a good job of including an outline of her presentation in her introduction. What does the speaker say she will discuss first in the presentation?",
    "answers": ["the definition of cyberbullying"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important for speakers to define key terms that audience members should know in order to follow the presentation. The speaker does a good job of this by defining cyberbullying. What is the basic definition she gives?",
    "answers": ["Cyberbullying is harassment through technology"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which type of speech do you stand up and talk in front of your peers?",
    "answers": ["oral"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the questions that follow. Question 5 Clip (This will open in a new window.) Play Video What phrase does the speaker use to shift to the outline of the speech?",
    "answers": ["Today, ..."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker mentions that the topic of her presentation is “cyberbullying”. However, like any good presenter, she also has a more narrow focus, or controlling idea. She uses the phrase “ties in with” to introduce the more specific issue related to cyberbullying. What is this idea?",
    "answers": ["right to free speech"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For questions 6-10, you need to refer to the following video. Watch the video and answer the questions that follow. Questions 6-10 Video (This will open in a new window.)",
    "answers": ["oral", "to inform"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker does a good job of including an outline of her presentation in her introduction. What does the speaker say she will discuss last in the presentation?",
    "answers": ["a solution for cyberbullying"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At the end of the presentation, the speaker shares her opinion, per the request of an audience member. What is the speaker’s opinion about the topic?",
    "answers": [
      "She thinks that cyberbullying needs to be more clearly defined by schools and states."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of presentation is this?",
    "answers": ["poster", "Video presentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. To conclude her presentation, the speaker says ________________.",
    "answers": ["Thank you for watching."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mode of persuasion is about the step-by-step, logical development of your arguments?",
    "answers": ["logos"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you are given the freedom to organize your speech, how many sections should you create for the body?",
    "answers": ["2-5 sections"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is NOT a formal assessment?",
    "answers": [
      "Asking your classmates or colleagues whether you did a good job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of verbal delivery?",
    "answers": ["Audibility"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is an example of nonverbal delivery?",
    "answers": ["Eye contact"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the description here to the correct term below. exceptions to a rule",
    "answers": ["caveat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the description here to the correct term below. the use of an author’s words without saying the author’s name",
    "answers": ["plagiarism"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some ways to give your audience an epiphany in the conclusion of your presentation? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "tell about the future",
      "synthesize the points by explaining how they fit together",
      "call for action",
      "use a quotation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you are giving a presentation about homelessness. You want to end your presentation with a call for action. Which of these endings is the best example of this technique?",
    "answers": [
      "Let’s come together and spread awareness about our homeless population."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. When someone asks a question, it is a good idea to ________________.",
    "answers": [
      "respond to the inquirer as well as everyone else in the audience"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true, according to the lessons from this week?",
    "answers": [
      "If there are still questions to be answered when the presentation has ended, the presenter may offer his/her time to speak with individuals one-on-one following the presentation."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "While reading a script or notecards word-for-word is not recommended in a speech, __________ should always be read verbatim (word-for-word).",
    "answers": ["quotations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to this course, what is the best way to see yourself rehearse?",
    "answers": [
      "by setting the camera up in such a way that you can record your whole body"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Considering time, it is best to ___________.",
    "answers": [
      "discreetly keep an eye on the clock while rehearsing and during your actual presentation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ideally, you should rehearse your presentation __________.",
    "answers": ["several times"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If there is a microphone in the room, what is an appropriate way to test it?",
    "answers": ["speak over the microphone at your normal volume"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean to inflect one’s voice?",
    "answers": ["to change the its tone or stress"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Having a banana may be a good pre-presentation snack.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Slowing down your speech will help with nerves.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to have sound effects in your PowerPoint to make it more interesting.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to stand in front of your PowerPoint slides to encourage your audience to read them.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Effective co-presenting enhances a presentation rather than hinder it.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best title for a poster?",
    "answers": ["Increasing Productivity through Employee Motivation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the phrase: “Would you like a minute to look at the poster, or would you like for me to explain it to you?”",
    "answers": ["To see if the viewer prefers to read or chat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which title below uses correct capitalization?",
    "answers": [
      "The Consequences of Global Warming",
      "Diving into the Field of Hydrology",
      "The Case for School Uniforms",
      "A Day in the Life of an Ant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the “works cited” or “suggested reading” section of a handout, which part goes first?",
    "answers": ["The author’s last name"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you do between subheadings in a handout?",
    "answers": ["Leave a blank line"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For which type of publication is it NOT possible to use “mirrored” sections?",
    "answers": ["A novel being read in a literature class"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the description here to the correct term below. the comparison of two related ideas",
    "answers": ["analogy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the parts of an effective presentation conclusion?",
    "answers": ["summary, epiphany, thanks, questions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to print handouts in color for your presentation.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two parts of a speech should be memorized?",
    "answers": ["the hook and the epiphany"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The purpose of rephrasing a question is to _______________. (choose two)",
    "answers": [
      "make sure everyone else has heard the question clearly",
      "ensure you understand it (as the presenter)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Pacing back and forth is a good way to keep calm during your presentation.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It is not okay to be humorous during your presentation.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true regarding the proper usage of a microphone?",
    "answers": ["Your mouth should be about 8 inches away from the microphone."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to have your presentation saved in three places when you prepare to present: on a flash drive, on a cloud service, and printed for back up.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is optional when providing your contact information on a handout?",
    "answers": ["Your email address"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Co-presenters must agree on what the goal of their presentation is, such as to persuade, to inform, or to evaluate.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follow. Question 1 Clip Play Video What type of hook was used?",
    "answers": ["Telling a true story"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follow. Question 2 Clip Play Video How did the speaker show the relevance of the topic to the audience?",
    "answers": [
      "By saying “I chose a topic that you probably love as much as I do: shopping"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follow. Question 3 Clip Play Video Why might the speaker not have said her name at the beginning of her speech?",
    "answers": ["She didn't need to."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the questions that follow. Question 4 Clip Play Video What type of hook was not used?",
    "answers": ["Use a prop"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For which type of presentation is it important to dress appropriately and be fully prepared?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of presentation generally lasts longer?",
    "answers": ["Formal presentations", "Group presentations"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which type is a speech in which you stand up and talk in front of your peers?",
    "answers": ["Oral presentations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the link below and listen to a clip from an academic presentation. Then decide if the clip is from the introduction, body, or conclusion portions of the presentations. Question 1 Clip Play Video Which part of the presentation does this clip come from?",
    "answers": ["conclusion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the link below and listen to a clip from an academic presentation. Then decide if the clip is from the introduction, body, or conclusion portions of the presentations. Question 2 Clip Play Video Which part of the presentation does this clip come from?",
    "answers": ["body"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the link below and listen to a clip from an academic presentation. Then decide if the clip is from the introduction, body, or conclusion portions of the presentations. Question 3 Clip Play Video Which part of the presentation does this clip come from?",
    "answers": ["body"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? I’ve broken down this presentation into four sections.",
    "answers": ["outline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? I decided to research this subject because my father is a victim of this disease.",
    "answers": ["context"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? Hopefully, this information will make the world safer for us and our children.",
    "answers": ["context"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? At the end of the presentation, I will answer any questions that you still have.",
    "answers": ["outline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of a speech is the most nutritious?",
    "answers": ["The body"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a presentation that lasts 8-10 minutes, approximately how long should the body be?",
    "answers": ["6 minutes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best way to check the length of your speech?",
    "answers": ["Time the rehearsal of your speech."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video The speaker is explaining her experience with some of the residents at a retirement home. Her oral definition of aphasia was...",
    "answers": [
      "clearly written on her slide but not clearly articulated orally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 2 Clip Play Video In this excerpt, the presenter relies on...",
    "answers": ["expert testimony"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 3 Clip Play Video Although this excerpt is taken from the introduction of a speech, the speaker does an excellent job of providing examples to help explain what he means by “climate change driven by man-made activities” Identify the two examples he gives of these types of activities.",
    "answers": ["burning fossil fuels", "destroying forests"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What two methods does this lesson offer for making your ideas easy to remember and understand?",
    "answers": ["simplification and repetition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To simplify complex ideas, it is important to focus on...",
    "answers": ["people and ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method of simplification is the phrase below used for? suppose...",
    "answers": ["example"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method of simplification is the phrase below used for? ...is like...",
    "answers": ["analogy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to this lesson, which statement is true?",
    "answers": [
      "Saying “That’s all,” to conclude sounds lazy, boring and unsatisfying."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. After summarizing, it is a good idea to leave your audience with an epiphany. All of the following are techniques for doing so EXCEPT ________________.",
    "answers": ["asking for comments from the audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Synthesizing is a way of _________________.",
    "answers": [
      "showing how all the ideas within the presentation connect together"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. You can state your preference regarding questions from the audience _______________.",
    "answers": ["during the introduction"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. One way to anticipate potential questions is to consider ________________.",
    "answers": ["the opposing argument to your central argument"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. When an audience member asks a question, it is a good idea to _______________.",
    "answers": ["pause briefly to allow yourself time to think"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? According to the guidelines in this lesson, it is unacceptable to rely on any sort of notes while presenting.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This lesson mentions that using an outline may be beneficial because it allows the speaker to be ____________.",
    "answers": ["flexible"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When using a slideshow, it is important to __________ right before the presentation begins.",
    "answers": ["preload it on the computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about speakers?",
    "answers": [
      "We tend to speak faster in conversation than in formal presentations."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In this lesson, it is mentioned that one may speak faster when he/she is excited or slower when conveying something serious. What is true with regards to this idea?",
    "answers": [
      "It may be appropriate for a presenter to vary the speed of his/her speech if it serves a communicative purpose."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Regarding “shouting” at your audience, which statement is true?",
    "answers": ["Shouting is never appropriate during a presentation."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The following video clips illustrate common verbal and nonverbal blunders novice presenters may make. Identify the shortcoming of the presenter in each clip. Notice how these behaviors might distract the audience, and remember to avoid making these blunders when you present! Question 1 Clip Play Video",
    "answers": ["The presenter points at the audience."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 4 Clip Play Video",
    "answers": [
      "The presenter uses too many fillers.",
      "The presenter speaks too quickly/ does not pause.",
      "true"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Making an outline will help to alleviate nerves during the presentation.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Having a cup of coffee or a some candy before the presentation will give you more energy and help you to make it through the presentation.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Do not arrive early to the presentation. You will feel awkward and you may have to talk to the audience before it’s time.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #2. Tip #2: Use high-contrast ______.",
    "answers": ["colors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #4. Tip #4: Add ______ evidence.",
    "answers": ["visual"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #6. Tip #6: Don’t ______ to yourself.",
    "answers": ["talk"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is co presenting?",
    "answers": ["Presenting with one or more companions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should the other presenter do while one presenter is speaking?",
    "answers": ["stand out of the way but listen and watch"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If co-presenters want to convince the audience of the validity of their opinion, what is their aim?",
    "answers": ["to persuade"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you digitally create a poster with software like PowerPoint, print every item on a separate slide.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When digitally generating a poster with software like PowerPoint or Photoshop, add colorful graphics in the borders.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If most of your content is not laid out neatly in columns, add arrows or numbers to each section.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which area does this poster need improvement?",
    "answers": ["Text style", "Flow indicators", "Flow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much white (empty) space is there?",
    "answers": ["Too much"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To ______ the main ideas of a presentation",
    "answers": ["summarize"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To cover information that you didn’t have enough ______ to give",
    "answers": ["time"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To present data that is too ______ for other means",
    "answers": ["complicated"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why should you limit a handout to 1-2 pages?",
    "answers": ["Too much information will not help the audience."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 1A 4.4handouts1a.pdf PDF File Handout 1C 4.4handouts1c.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["1A"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 2A 4.4handouts2a.pdf PDF File Handout 2B 4.4handouts2b.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["2B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 3A 4.4handouts3a.pdf PDF File Handout 3C 4.4handouts3c.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["3A"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 4B 4.4handouts4b.pdf PDF File Handout 4C 4.4handouts4c.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["4B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the questions that follow. Question 1 Clip Play Video How did she get the audience’s involvement?",
    "answers": ["They raised their hands."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? Hello, everyone. Today, I’m going to tell you about the art of knitting.",
    "answers": ["greeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When preparing a speech, what should you do first?",
    "answers": ["Understand the task instructions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how fast should a presenter speak?",
    "answers": ["130 words per minute"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video To help the audience understand the symptoms of aphasia, the speaker...",
    "answers": ["gives an example"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 2 Clip Play Video In this excerpt, the presenter is avoiding ________________ by giving credit to the original source of the story.",
    "answers": ["plagiarism"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As a presenter, you do not want to...",
    "answers": ["lose your audience"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 3 Clip Play Video In this excerpt, the speaker defines a key term. Listen for the phrase he uses that indicates he will be giving a definition. Complete the sentence with the appropriate phrase: “My interest was around this part, the Sierra Nevada. It’s an asymmetrical mountain range, ____________________________________ if I were to split it in half, both of those sides wouldn’t be the same.”",
    "answers": ["meaning that"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. In your conclusion, the summary of your main points should be ________________.",
    "answers": ["brief"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This lesson mentions two important modes of delivery. What are they? (Choose two.)",
    "answers": ["script", "outline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy is mentioned in this lesson as a way of keeping your notecards properly ordered?",
    "answers": ["numbering them"]
  },
  {
    "question": "About how many words per minute does an effective presenter speak?",
    "answers": ["130"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The following video clips illustrate common verbal and nonverbal blunders (mistakes) novice presenters may make. Identify the shortcoming of the presenter in each clip. Notice how these behaviors might distract the audience, and remember to avoid making these blunders when you present! Question 1 Clip Play Video",
    "answers": ["The presenter seems to lack confidence."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 2 Clip Play Video",
    "answers": [
      "The presenter is moving her legs in a distracting way.",
      "Valid",
      "The presenter does not speak with inflection.",
      "at her office hours",
      "Deductive inference",
      "Mathematical necessity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 3 Clip Play Video",
    "answers": [
      "The presenter has her back to the audience.",
      "Deductive inference",
      "Invalid",
      "She presented a surprising fact.",
      "housekeeping"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine you offer an epiphany by saying, “This brings us back to the question I asked you at the beginning of my presentation.” In this case, what technique would you be using?",
    "answers": ["tieback"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #1. Tip #1: Choose a ______ template.",
    "answers": ["simple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Co presenting is much more difficult than presenting alone.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what kind of organization do co-presenters organize the content of their presentation through showing their audience rather than telling them?",
    "answers": ["demonstration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? You do not want to have visual aids that will distract your audience from you, the star of the presentation.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To illustrate a ______ point in more detail",
    "answers": ["particular"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should be at the bottom of the handout?",
    "answers": ["Works cited"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 1A 4.4handouts1a.pdf PDF File Handout 1B 4.4handouts1b.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["1A"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 2B 4.4handouts2b.pdf PDF File Handout 2C 4.4handouts2c.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["2B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 4A 4.4handouts4a.pdf PDF File Handout 4B 4.4handouts4b.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["4B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The Mission Statement is explains how the university, school, and program will meet their goals in the next 5 years.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker mentioned that some schools offer a “thesis Masters and a non-thesis Masters”. What idea was he supporting when he said this?",
    "answers": ["Curriculum"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker said “I’m not talking about if they have a gym or a library” as he discussed what topic that could be included in the Research Paragraph?",
    "answers": ["Facilities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement do you think the speaker would probably NOT agree with?",
    "answers": [
      "You should not use your own positive qualities in the research paragraph.",
      "Following exactly what your parents tell you to do is the best way to become a scientist."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the Research Paragraph?",
    "answers": [
      "To show how the student and the university are good for each other"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You should have already listened to the Note-Taking Assignment 1 lecture. Use your notes to answer the questions. What are the main ideas of the lecture?",
    "answers": [
      "Qualities of a lecture and a learner that make lectures difficult"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The topic of the lecture is characteristics of a learner that make comprehension of a lecture difficult.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of how a speaker “delivers” a lecture?",
    "answers": ["How clearly the examples support the main idea"]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 2 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. What would be a good way to signal a “definition” in your lecture notes?",
    "answers": ["Def"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When should you fill in the section at the bottom of the page when using a Cornell Notes template?",
    "answers": ["after the lecture"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following topics will be presented third in the class?",
    "answers": ["development of the general principle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk. Take thorough notes using one of the templates you've been given. Then answer all of the questions that follow. Play Video The speaker says he was diagnosed with severe Attention Deficit Disorder (ADD) in the early 80s. This was not a positive diagnosis. How do you know, from the lecture, that it was not positive? (Choose 2 of the following answers.)",
    "answers": [
      "The speaker says, “ . . . not a diagnosis that you wanted in the early 80’s”.",
      "The speaker says, \"People diagnosed with ADD were treated as if they needed to be fixed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reason that the speaker told the story of the man he met in the fish market in Panama?",
    "answers": [
      "To give an example of how everyone is connected to social media"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what order did the speaker list groups of people that understand how important it is to make an emotional connection with people?",
    "answers": ["Businesses, non-profits, political institutions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Using pauses to signal important information is an example of a language clue.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Language cues signal that a certain kind of information is about to be given.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following ideas do you think the speaker would NOT agree with?",
    "answers": [
      "Reviewing your notes for the first time one week after the lecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk titled “Embrace Your Disobedience” by Diego Rosso. Take thorough notes using one of the templates you've been given. Then answer all of the questions that follow. Lecture Clip Play Video How did the speaker get the audience to focus on his topic at the beginning of his presentation?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the speaker tell the story about the student who visited him in his office?",
    "answers": ["To show how a professor can learn from a student."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following clip from the talk and answer the question below. Short Clip Play Video What does the speaker mean?",
    "answers": [
      "The speaker will feel successful if his research about bubbles helps someone else to do something great, even if he is not remembered."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these items from the introduction of a lecture should be put in your notes? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "the main points if they are mentioned",
      "the topic of the lecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The questions should guide you in observing important aspects of the introduction. The questions will aim to make sure that you have understood the important content that the professor is trying to communicate. Listen to the lecture clip, and choose the best and most specific answer to each question. Question 1 Clip Play Video Why does Dr. Ferguson think it is important for everyone to learn about Earth System Science?",
    "answers": [
      "Because many of the world’s problems are related to Earth System Science"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of important information is often given in the introduction of a lecture? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["the organization of the lecture", "the topic of the lecture"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 6 Clip Play Video Which kind of information from the introduction does the clip contain? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Topic and organization", "Hook"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the video clip taken from a longer lecture called “The Distracted Mind,” given by Professor Gazzaley. Take notes on your own paper. Do your best to identify the main idea and details from the lecture segment and to write them in indented form as you learned to do in the Main Idea video lecture. Then answer the following questions. Lecture Clip Play Video True or false? The main idea of this lecture is how amazing the brain is.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Professor Gazzaley named the three limitations the beginning, but presented them in a different order. What order did he NAME the 3 limitations of the brain in the beginning of his talk?",
    "answers": ["attention, working memory, speed"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he mentions the “spotlight” view. What limitation is he describing when he talks about the “spotlight” view?",
    "answers": ["attention"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker mentioned the statistics that “in India where 17% of the world’s population lives, only has 4% of the world’s fresh water and of that 2⁄3 of it is already polluted and is unfit for human consumption.” What idea do these statistics support?",
    "answers": [
      "There is going to be a severe shortage of clean water in the future."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language cues were used in this talk?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When the word “smashed” was emphasized, people recalled that cars were going faster and they reported that there was broken glass at the accident, even though in reality there wasn’t.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What cue helps us identify the important information of what Dr. Loftus studies?",
    "answers": ["longer pauses"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you know that the number 300 is an important number to pay attention to? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The number 300 is repeated twice.",
      "The number 300 is spoken more slowly.",
      "The number 300 is spoken in a higher pitch."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After Dr. Loftus describes three experiments, she uses the following language cue to signal the general conclusion of the studies: “so what these studies are showing is that . . “. What was the general conclusion?",
    "answers": ["You can change or distort what people remember."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Look at this transcript from part of the video you just watched. Words that are repeated and create parallel structures are underlined. What important point is being made? “In one project in the United States, information has been gathered on 300 innocent people, 300 defendants who were convicted of crimes they didn't do. They spent 10, 20, 30 years in prison for these crimes, and now DNA testing has proven that they are actually innocent. And when those cases have been analyzed, three quarters of them are due to faulty memory, faulty eyewitness memory.”",
    "answers": [
      "Innocent people were put in jail because witnesses remembered something that really didn’t happen."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Directly after Dr. Loftus says “three quarters of them are due to faulty memory”, she uses the phrase “But why?” What information does this language cue signal?",
    "answers": [
      "The reason jurors believed the witnesses said things that were not true"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Video Clip Play Video What is the purpose of the study?",
    "answers": [
      "To find out American’s perception about whether crime is getting better or worse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 4 Video Clip Play Video In which year did Americans feel least concerned about crime in the U.S.?",
    "answers": ["2005"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip that belongs with each question. Then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video This argument was implied in the lecture: Premise 1: People of equal intelligence ask the same questions about the things they see. Premise 2: The people living 100,000 years ago were as smart as we are. Premise 3: The people living 100,000 years ago saw the same sky we see. Conclusion: Therefore, people living 100,000 years ago asked the same questions about the sky that we ask. Is this argument valid?",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip that belongs with each question. Then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video The belief that no one has photographic memory is a:",
    "answers": ["An inductive inference"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the questions that follow. Question 4 Clip (This will open in a new window.) Play Video Which phrase does the speaker use to start transitioning from her hook to the topic of the presentation?",
    "answers": ["Over my last two years..."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Ebbinhaus's study found that eventually people forget everything when the retention interval is very long.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good ways that you can show that you are interested in what your group members have to say? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Lean in with your body.",
      "Nod in agreement with what they are saying.",
      "Smile as they speak."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It is better to speak spontaneously without planning a response in a group discussion so that the conversation does not change direction while you are planning what you want to say.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you truly believe that “everyone you will ever meet knows something you don’t,” what is the most productive way for you to respond?",
    "answers": [
      "To actively seek what you can learn from every person that you meet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. Preparing for an academic discussion is like building a house because ____________________.",
    "answers": ["for both, you must start by laying the groundwork."]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you’re taking double-entry notes to prepare for a discussion, what should you NOT do?",
    "answers": ["Take notes only on your personal reaction to the ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of preparing a list of points that you’d like to make during a discussion?",
    "answers": [
      "To give you ideas for possible contributions you could make to the discussion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. When you introduce yourself, ____________________.",
    "answers": ["say your name"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. An example of clearly addressing the question is when the topic says, “Discuss the reasons for the high cost of university tuition,” and the group starts talking about _________________.",
    "answers": ["what causes universities to raise tuition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. An academic discussion should be ___________________.",
    "answers": [
      "like riding the rapids in a raft with everyone working equally to navigate the waters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. intrinsic ____________",
    "answers": ["value"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you elaborate, you ________________.",
    "answers": ["add more information"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some ways to elaborate in a discussion?",
    "answers": ["By giving analogies, hypotheticals, facts, and anecdotes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is NOT a good sentence frame for encouraging other people to elaborate in a discussion?",
    "answers": ["Can you please try to be more succinct?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you characterize this quote from an academic conversation? “You might think that there’s plenty of water in the world, but in fact, only 3% of the world’s water is freshwater. People believe that the world has an endless supply of water, but most of it is saltwater.” It is ______________.",
    "answers": ["repetitive"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a discussion about literacy, someone cites the percentage of people who can’t read in the U.S. This is an example of a ____________.",
    "answers": ["a statistic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are considered lower level thinking? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["knowledge", "comprehension"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are critical thinking skills? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "to support one’s ideas with related evidence",
      "to apply what was learned to new situations",
      "to think of different possibilities",
      "to find patterns in seemingly unrelated ideas",
      "to see things from different points of view",
      "to give an opinion with relevant support"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When critical thinking is integrated into a discussion group, the concepts discussed in the group will be remembered longer than if they had only used lower-level thinking skills.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking does the following question represent? “What, in our opinion, is the best way to educate the population about the dangers of genetically modified foods?”",
    "answers": ["evaluation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. anecdotal _____________",
    "answers": ["evidence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. pivotal ___________",
    "answers": ["role"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an appropriate statement to get the discussion back on track?",
    "answers": [
      "“We are running out of time and we haven’t answered all of the question yet.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you do if someone is acting bored or just not saying anything?",
    "answers": ["Invite that person to participate."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are mentioned as important to do when constructing a conversation? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Accomplishing the assigned task",
      "Gathering background knowledge of the conversation topic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which concept of constructing a conversation is illustrated by the following? (Match the parts of the analogy.) the blueprint",
    "answers": [
      "The task guides the development of the topic and provides focus for all of the group members."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true for a discourse community?",
    "answers": [
      "Disagreement can lead to a better conversation--if it’s done the right way."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the two words that complete the sentence correctly. To keep a discussion collaborative--not confrontational--you need to be _________ and use _________.",
    "answers": ["logical; evidence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of these phrases of disagreement, which will probably help your conversation partner to save face?",
    "answers": ["I see your point, but I can’t agree."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of these phrases of disagreement, which will be least likely to add to a collaborative feeling in your discussion group?",
    "answers": ["Seriously?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. become _____________",
    "answers": ["the focus"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. vast ______________",
    "answers": ["majority"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Synthesis in a discussion involves all of the following elements except _____________.",
    "answers": [
      "including every idea mentioned during the discussion in the conclusion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When synthesizing, you can pull together information from _______________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To form a synthesis of ideas at the end of a discussion, you should ______________.",
    "answers": ["allow for a little time to reflect"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not essential, according to this lesson, when ending a group discussion?",
    "answers": ["being sure to use sentence frames"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following statements from a discussion on what we can personally do to combat population growth. - “We need to be more mindful of our consumption of natural resources, such as taking shorter showers.” - “Do think that really helps? That seems like a drop in the bucket. If I take a shorter shower, it is not going to affect the people in India.” - “I agree. Even if you do these things, not everyone will. I think what we need to do is to make other people aware of the problem instead of just working on yourself.” - “I personally think that population growth, environmental issues, and poverty are all related to education. Education is the solution to these problems. Education will help people make better decisions that will impact the negative effect people have on the earth and how we get along with each other.” What is the best synthesizing statement below for the the ideas above?",
    "answers": [
      "Although being mindful of our personal usage of natural resources is a good thing to do, it will not really make much of an impact on population growth. We need to educate and make people aware of the problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? An action point is the task that is assigned to an individual in the group as a result of the discussion.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following image represent in a a conversation?",
    "answers": [
      "Be sure to synthesize your ideas throughout your discussion and again at the end."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. effective _____________",
    "answers": ["policy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. enormous _____________",
    "answers": ["impact"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. give ___________",
    "answers": ["consideration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why would you want to ask your conversation partners to elaborate? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "So that you can have enough information to respond to",
      "So that you can truly understand what they’re trying to say"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you characterize this quote from an academic conversation? “Water scarcity is a serious problem that affects the entire world. We must do something about it.” It is _______________.",
    "answers": ["lacking in specificity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you characterize this quote from an academic conversation? “We will see an increase in the scarcity of water in the near future. In fact, two-thirds of the world’s population may experience water shortages by the year 2025.” It is _____________.",
    "answers": ["well elaborated"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a discussion about urban sprawl, someone tells a story about growing up in the countryside. This is an example of _____________.",
    "answers": ["an anecdote"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When critical thinking is integrated into a discussion group, the concepts discussed in the group can be applied more easily to different situations than if they had only used lower-level thinking skills.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following phrases does NOT require deeper, or critical, thinking?",
    "answers": ["What did the professor say about . . . .?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It is more important what you say rather than how you say it.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you want to remember a new word to use in a discussion, which of the following is most important to do?",
    "answers": ["Use the word in your own example sentence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. To get ready for your discussion, you should do all of the following EXCEPT ________________.",
    "answers": ["have your strategy for how to win the conversation ready"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A common mistake in starting an academic conversation happens when _________________.",
    "answers": ["not everyone understands the discussion topic clearly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. During your discussion it is good to be aware of all except _________________.",
    "answers": ["what is happening on your phone"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you do if there is disagreement among discussion participants?",
    "answers": ["Keep calm and respectful. Disagreement is normal."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which concept of constructing a conversation is illustrated by the following? (Match the parts of the analogy.) the foundation of a house",
    "answers": [
      "A solid discussion relies and rests on background knowledge and understanding the value of the conversation."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. _________________ adds to a conversation because hearing a diversity of opinions helps you to develop your own ideas.",
    "answers": ["Disagreement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you concede a point, it means that you are basically saying ____________.",
    "answers": ["“I agree with part of what you said.”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. conventional ____________",
    "answers": ["wisdom"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. basic ______________",
    "answers": ["premise"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important that the final synthesis be logical and organized. The term for this is ______________.",
    "answers": ["coherent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What needs to be done to get the most out of the conversation, according to the video lesson? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Organize the ideas that were discussed in logical groups so that they are easier to remember.",
      "Decide on next steps and action points.",
      "Self-assess to see if you accomplished the group task."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The best academic discussion involves everyone contributing their ideas, opinions, and experiences so that new perspectives and ideas can form.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? As long as everyone can hear each other’s voice clearly, it does not matter if the group members can see each other’s faces or not.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A good discussion never has time where no one is speaking.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you start your discussion, you should ________________. (Choose two answers.)",
    "answers": [
      "clear the desk tops of unnecessary items",
      "see the discussion participants as teammates",
      "introduce yourselves",
      "make sure everyone understands the topic to be discussed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Look at the picture of a group discussion. Then look at the problems and solutions listed below. Choose one problem and one solution that match the picture.",
    "answers": [
      "Solution: Organize yourselves so that all participants are on an equal level and can see each other easily.",
      "Problem: Students are not in a position to talk because their backs are to each other."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After you watch the two improved videos of the discussion on water scarcity, answer the following questions about David’s academic conversation skills. True or false? David is prepared for the discussion.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip. In what ways is it apparent that David is listening to understand in this short video clip? Choose all that apply. Play Video",
    "answers": [
      "He nods his head.",
      "He says “yeah”, “hmmm” and “right”.",
      "He has good eye contact.",
      "He makes a related comment connect to what was said.",
      "He leans in with his body."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video of David asking a question. What higher level thinking skill is David challenging his group members to perform? Play Video",
    "answers": ["evaluation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what ways can David use his voice and gestures more dynamically? He could _______________.",
    "answers": ["all of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an anecdote?",
    "answers": ["a brief story"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of example for supporting your ideas is this? My friend had her computer hacked when she clicked on a link in an email.",
    "answers": ["anecdote"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of example for supporting your ideas is this? A good essay is like a hamburger, with the bun being the introduction and conclusion....",
    "answers": ["analogy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hypotheticals usually begin with all of the following except ____________.",
    "answers": ["I know a man who . . ."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are considered higher level thinking? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["evaluation", "synthesis", "analysis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking requires learners to bring different ideas together to form something totally new?",
    "answers": ["synthesis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking requires learners to state an opinion and support it with evidence?",
    "answers": ["evaluation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking does the following question represent? “Is it better to have lots of GM food available to feed more people or to limit GM food in order to protect people from unknown health risks?”",
    "answers": ["evaluation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of genetically modified foods. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video When Chad asks, “What do you mean by ‘beneficial’?” Troy answers, “Is it good? Like, do you think it is good?” Why is Troy’s response not helpful in motivating the academic discussion?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below of a group discussing the following question: Do you think that GM foods are good for society? Then answer the question below. Play Video Which of the following phrases communicates that there is one clear and correct answer?",
    "answers": ["I can tell you certainly that they are good for society."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below of a group discussing the following question: Do you think that GM foods are good for society? Then answer the question below. Play Video True or false? Jackie thinks that GM foods are good for society.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of genetically modified foods. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video In this video clip, the group members are analyzing the information given to them by the professor. Which of the statements below is the most logical conclusion based on the given information? Given information: “In 50 countries, there are significant restrictions or outright bans on GMOs.”",
    "answers": [
      "There must be a reason why so many countries do not support GM foods. We should study the risks more carefully."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If someone isn’t participating in the discussion you should leave that person alone.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? A person who doesn’t say anything during the discussion has an equally bad effect as someone who talks too much.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Disagreement among participants can improve a discussion.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Decide if the statement below is appropriate for the given situation or not. Situation: Someone is looking bored and not participating. You say to them: “If you're bored, you can leave.”",
    "answers": ["No, it's not appropriate."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the video lecture, which of the following are mentioned as important to do when constructing a conversation? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Analyzing, synthesizing, or evaluating a comment made by your group",
      "Being motivated by understanding why the discussion is important",
      "Preventing your group from having a conversation on an irrelevant topic",
      "Doing the assigned homework related to the topic",
      "Referencing your partner’s comment as you share your own idea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Background knowledge is attained only by the homework that the teacher assigns on the topic.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Which quote from this clip shows that the conversation partners are trying to honor and build on their partners’ earlier ideas?",
    "answers": [
      "“I think that’s a really interesting point and something I hadn’t thought about before.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video At the end of the clip, Chad says, “Would we agree that water scarcity is the biggest problem of population growth?” Why does he ask this?",
    "answers": [
      "To get the group back on track and focused on the discussion objectives"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Later in the clip, how does Kevin show that he partially agrees with Dana?",
    "answers": ["“I agree in a way, but not completely.”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Which is a true statement about this part of the discussion?",
    "answers": ["Everyone agrees with Dana’s point."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video When Cameron is speaking, how do Dana and Kevin show that they’re listening attentively?",
    "answers": ["A, B, and C"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word below that matches this definition: the pulling together of data from different sources to support one’s ideas and combining all the information to create something new",
    "answers": ["synthesis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word below that matches this definition: logical and organized",
    "answers": ["coherent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Everyone in a discussion must agree with each other at the end.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following statements from a discussion on what the students think are the biggest problems of population growth. - “Water scarcity is the biggest problem of population growth. There is a serious lack of access to fresh water.” - “I think that future wars won’t be fought over oil but water.” - “Lack of education is one of the biggest problems of population growth. It always comes back to education.“ - “True, lack of education is a big problem of population growth; it can also be part of the solution. “ What is the best synthesizing statement for the ideas above?",
    "answers": [
      "While water is the most endangered natural resource, the lack of education fuels not only issues with natural resources but social and economic problems as well."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are sentence frames that would precede a statement of synthesis? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Our take-away from this discussion is . . .",
      "Based on what we have discussed, we should probably . . .",
      "This discussion has led us on a journey that took us from . . . to . . .",
      "How can we bring this all together?",
      "What can we all agree on?",
      "What is our take-away?",
      "What is the common denominator in all that we have discussed?",
      "How can we synthesize our conversation?",
      "What is the general consensus?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The action points that are discussed at the end of the discussion are the most interesting topics that were brought up.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video This is a good example of an introduction to an academic discussion because:",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video A family has an income of less than $30 a month. What kind of poverty is this family experiencing?",
    "answers": ["Absolute poverty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video What are some things that the group facilitator does to encourage group participation?",
    "answers": ["All of the above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Which of the following were mentioned as causes of poverty in the video clip? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The growing population",
      "Poor government policy and the poor management of money",
      "Lack of education"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The best academic discussion is where the smartest and most experienced person in the group shares his/her knowledge and the group members ask relevant questions.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important that the group discussion stays on task and on topic. Which of the following are acceptable ways to refocus the group back on the goal of the discussion? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Say “I think we are getting a little off topic.”",
      "Say “Let’s get back on track, everyone.”",
      "Say “We are running short on time, so let’s get back to the main point.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As David began the discussion, which of the following did he do?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statements describe how David communicates clearly? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "He uses sentence frames and language cues.",
      "He reads listeners’ gestures and adjusts accordingly."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of example for supporting your ideas is this? What if there weren’t enough water in developed nations now...?",
    "answers": ["hypothetical"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking requires learners to break down material into smaller parts in order to understand the structure of the concept better?",
    "answers": ["analysis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below of a group discussing the following question: Do you think that GM foods are good for society? Then answer the question below. Play Video Chad cannot decide if GM foods are beneficial to society. According to his response, what would help him make a decision?",
    "answers": ["More research on the effects of GM foods on the human body"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If someone is talking too much, you should let that person continue as long as they have ideas.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Understanding the value of a group discussion can motivate you to come prepared and to fully participate in the discussion. Which of the following questions can help you reflect on the value of the discussion?",
    "answers": ["All of the above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two benefits of having background knowledge of the discussion topic, according to the video? (Select two answers.)",
    "answers": [
      "You will be able to keep the discussion on focus because you will have an idea of the scope of the discussion.",
      "You will be able to contribute more insightful information for your group members to think about."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Decide if the statement below is appropriate for the given situation or not. Situation: Someone is talking too much. You say to them: “That’s interesting, but we haven’t heard from everyone yet.”",
    "answers": ["Yes, it's appropriate."]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the questions in this activity refer to the following situation: Megan and Brendan are having a discussion in an Intro to Music class. The topic of the discussion is \"Which musical genres will be most relevant to future generations of music fans?\" For each question, click on the Statement link. Then listen to each answer response and pay attention to how the other speaker disagrees with the statement. Choose the statement that sounds more collaborative, or polite, and less confrontational. Statement 1 Which response below is less confrontational?",
    "answers": ["Response B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Statement 2 Which response below is less confrontational?",
    "answers": ["Response A"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Statement 3 Which response below is less confrontational?",
    "answers": ["Response B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video After Dana has made a point, Chad says, “I see that, but do you think that really helps?” Why doesn’t he just say, “Do you think that really helps?”",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video How does Dana defend her point in a collaborative and polite manner?",
    "answers": [
      "“That’s true and I see where all of you are coming from, but I still stand firm in my belief.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video At the end of the clip, how could Chad--the blond guy--improve his body language in order to create a better sense of community with his group members?",
    "answers": ["He could give everyone a high five after they speak."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word below that matches this definition: general agreement among group members",
    "answers": ["consensus"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word below that matches this definition: short, complete and to the point",
    "answers": ["concise"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Summary and synthesis are essentially the same thing.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video A family of four lives in a one-bedroom apartment and can usually pay rent each month, but only has money to eat one healthy meal a day. What kind of poverty is this family experiencing?",
    "answers": ["Extreme poverty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video A family has enough money to pay rent each month, to buy clothes to wear, and to eat three balanced meals a day, but they live in a bad area of town. They can only buy used clothing, and they can’t afford to eat out in restaurants. What kind of poverty is this family experiencing?",
    "answers": ["Relative poverty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following should you write in the space on the left when taking Cornell notes? Choose TWO answers.",
    "answers": ["study questions", "key vocabulary"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker says, “My family was a fairly proactive family . . . “ What does the term “proactive” mean?",
    "answers": ["Making things happen rather than reacting to events"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 6 Clip Play Video What does the professor say about repeated reading of the textbook?",
    "answers": [
      "Reading repeatedly might not be enough. Students should use more active study techniques."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is important about the number 300 in the lecture?",
    "answers": [
      "It is the number of people who were unfairly put in prison. (:53-1:25)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "For questions 1-3, listen to the lecture clip below on psychology and take notes as you listen. Pay attention to the information in the charts or graphs. After you listen, use your notes to answer the following questions. Question 1-3 Lecture Clip Play Video Prof. Steyvers mentions a study by Ebbinghuas. What did Ebbinghaus discover?",
    "answers": [
      "There is still some residual memory of the information no matter how long after the retrieval interval is."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 3 Video Clip Play Video The professor mentions over 50%. What does that percentage refer to?",
    "answers": [
      "Percentage of people whose perception of crime nationally is extremely serious or very serious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? A speaker's tone or stance may be interesting to the listener but are not very important for understanding a lecture.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video What question did the speaker ask the audience?",
    "answers": ["She didn't ask any questions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to this clip and answer the question that follow. Question 2 Play Video What background information was provided?",
    "answers": ["Why she selected this topic"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What public speaking tasks might an employee be asked to do?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of presentation is the most interactive (the one that is most conducive to one-on-one conversations)?",
    "answers": ["Poster presentations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? Then, we’ll look at the advantages and disadvantages of each option.",
    "answers": ["outline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? I’m an assistant manager at Lucky Burgers. I started working there in 2012.",
    "answers": ["greeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which part of a speech’s introduction would this sentence go? Good morning. It’s a pleasure to be here today.",
    "answers": ["greeting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If a speech were a burger, what part would the body be?",
    "answers": ["The juicy middle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "To help the audience remember your main points, you should follow which pattern?",
    "answers": ["assertion, evidence, assertion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method of simplification is the phrase below used for? upwards of...",
    "answers": ["approximation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method of simplification is the phrase below used for? ...is commonly called...",
    "answers": ["acronym"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. If the presenter does not mention his/her preference regarding the right time to ask questions, audience members may ask questions ________________.",
    "answers": [
      "any time during the presentation or following the presentation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. A good way to prepare for questions is to anticipate possible confusion audience members might have or clarification they may need while you are delivering ________________.",
    "answers": ["the body of your presentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An outline should _____________.",
    "answers": ["contain only short phrases or key words"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Verbal skills include all of the following EXCEPT ___________.",
    "answers": ["smiling while speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How loudly you speak depends on ____________.",
    "answers": ["the size of the room in which you are presenting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When an audience member seems to have a negative expression, smile at him/her and give him/her all your attention.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you remember something you forgot earlier, apologize to your audience and let them know what it is that you forgot to say.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #3. Tip #3: Increase the ______ size.",
    "answers": ["font"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the sentence from PowerPoint Tip #5. Tip #5: Write only the ______.",
    "answers": ["keywords"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a name for the concept that presenters want their audience to leave the presentation with?",
    "answers": ["a takeaway"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? To give a three-dimensional (3D) effect to poster items, you can layer blocks of text behind colored paper.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To act as an interactive, practical ______ that encourages critical thinking",
    "answers": ["worksheet"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Click on the links below and compare the two handouts. Then answer the question that follows. Handout 3A 4.4handouts3a.pdf PDF File Handout 3B 4.4handouts3b.pdf PDF File Based on the tips in this lesson, which handout is better?",
    "answers": ["3A"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A good discussion is most similar to _____________.",
    "answers": ["a volleyball match"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good ways to prepare for an academic discussion? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Read information on the topic in your textbook, in the library, and on the internet.",
      "Meet with your classmates and informally review what you know about the topic."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you start your discussion, you should ________________.",
    "answers": ["sit so everyone can see each other"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of example for supporting your ideas is this? Nearly 1 out of every 5 deaths under the age of 5 worldwide is due to a water-related diseases.",
    "answers": ["facts and statistics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An anecdote is mostly likely to begin with _____________.",
    "answers": ["When I worked at a company like that one . . ."]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? When a discussion group makes the effort to think more deeply and critically, the discussion is more engaging.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of genetically modified foods. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Which of the following is true about the group discussion?",
    "answers": [
      "The group members are not physically positioned in a way that motivates the members to do their best and to be involved in the discussion."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of genetically modified foods. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video In this video clip, the members politely challenged each other’s ideas. Which of the following phrases were used to politely challenge ideas that had been previously mentioned?",
    "answers": [
      "You know, Chad, maybe . . .",
      "I see your points, but . . .",
      "Even though . . .",
      "If they were so good, then why. . . .?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The goal of a discussion should always be agreement.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video What’s a quote from this clip that shows that the conversation partners are trying to build on each other’s ideas?",
    "answers": ["“Like you were saying . . .”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch the video clip below from an academic discussion on the topic of population growth. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video In the clip, Chad says, “To dovetail on what you said.” What does this mean?",
    "answers": ["To connect with what you said"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video Which of the following phrases from the video clip was used to synthesize ideas that were mentioned in the discussion?",
    "answers": ["“It sounds like what you guys are touching on is . . . “"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The speaker mentioned “swiping” as an example for what idea?",
    "answers": ["Games and apps"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? According to the lecture, culture is one thing that can make a lecture difficult for a listener.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The speaker uses language cues, visual cues, and verbal cues to make his points.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the speaker mean when he says, “One of the biggest problems people have is that they are too ambitious.”",
    "answers": ["People plan too much in their schedules."]
  },
  {
    "question": "When will special relativity be discussed in the course?",
    "answers": ["in the beginning of the course"]
  },
  {
    "question": "See how well you can determine meaning of an actual professor giving an introduction to Einstein’s General Relativity and Gravitation. The lecture is 4 minutes 39 seconds long. First, watch the entire video, then answer each of the following questions. General Relativity and Gravitation Lecture Loaded: 2.20% Play / Mute Settings Full Screen How does the professor know many of the students?",
    "answers": ["They took his class before"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following questions would not be appropriate to write in the “Questions/Main Ideas” column on a Cornell Note-taking form?",
    "answers": ["Why do we need to learn to manage time?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a hypothetical?",
    "answers": [
      "fictional situations used to examine possibilities of a situation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is NOT a way to show respect for your group members?",
    "answers": [
      "Think about what you are going to say next as they are speaking."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. integral ____________",
    "answers": ["part"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reaching a general agreement in a group is called ____________.",
    "answers": ["consensus"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A brief overview of main points is called ______________.",
    "answers": ["summary"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The action points that are discussed at the end of a discussion are the most interesting topics that were brought up.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following were frequently-referenced ideas in this course? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Be sure to build your background knowledge, or knowledge of the topic, before you have your discussion.",
      "Discussions are all about collaboration, so be sure to build on what other people say.",
      "Have a plan for your conversation, and try to follow it. Don’t get sidetracked."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. empirical _____________",
    "answers": ["evidence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. meet _____________",
    "answers": ["expectations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why should you elaborate in a discussion?",
    "answers": ["To clearly explain your ideas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. ample _______________",
    "answers": ["evidence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. pilot ___________",
    "answers": ["study"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to use the same template colors for all of your slides.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you need to temporarily step away from your poster, what should you do?",
    "answers": ["Ask a neighboring presenter to greet your viewers for you."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main reason why you should limit a handout to 1-2 pages?",
    "answers": ["Too much information will not help the audience."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of content?",
    "answers": ["Accuracy of information"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Match the description here to the correct term below. a chart, table, graph, or demonstration",
    "answers": ["illustration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. After offering an epiphany, the presenter should _____________.",
    "answers": ["smile, but remain standing silently for a few seconds"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Regarding rehearsing, all of the following are true EXCEPT __________.",
    "answers": [
      "Try rehearsing sitting down and standing up to get extra practice and become less nervous."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of a distracting verbal mannerism is _____________.",
    "answers": ["saying “um”"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of a distracting nonverbal mannerism is ___________.",
    "answers": ["touching your hair"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements do you think is NOT true about the speaker, based on his talk?",
    "answers": [
      "He thinks students should learn from professors and professors should not learn from their students."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk titled “Embrace Your Disobedience” by Diego Rosso. Take thorough notes using one of the templates you've been given. Then answer the questions that follow. Lecture Clip Play Video In the introduction, the speaker describes how he was as a child: “If they told me I shouldn’t have done something, I thought, ‘Who says? Why?’ and they got me in trouble, just about all the time and I had a special preference for dismantling things and never putting them back together.” How does this comment relate to the main idea of his talk?",
    "answers": [
      "It illustrates the speaker's point. The speaker’s personality of questioning the way things are helps him to be the researching professor he is today."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what order were the following people mentioned in the talk? (note: This kind of question checks how well your notes are organized.)",
    "answers": [
      "June Wayne, Channa Horowitz, the student who came in his office, Copernicus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following might be hooks in a lecture? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["a story", "interesting fact"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he mentions the “cocktail party effect.” What limitation is he describing when he talks about the “cocktail party effect”?",
    "answers": ["attention"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Professor Gazzaley was talking about one of the three limitations, he said, “It changes depending on complexity.” Which limitation is her referring to?",
    "answers": ["working memory"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? The speaker believes that there are many ways to define the term “sustainability.”",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the following TED talk titled “The Future of Water” by Bill Cooper. Take thorough notes on one of the templates you've been given. Do your best to identify the important information that you should put in your notes based on the video lesson you have just watched. Then answer the following questions. Lecture Clip (This will open in a new window.) The speaker mentions the walk he takes on campus everyday and all the birds and animal life he sees and hears. What idea does he want to support with this information?",
    "answers": ["That we need to care and connect with nature"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 2 Video Clip Play Video Which chart/graph did the professor use?",
    "answers": ["line graph"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 4 Video Clip Play Video Which chart/graph did the professor use in this clip?",
    "answers": ["line graph"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the lecture clip below and answer the question that follows. Question 3 Lecture Clip Play Video True or false? Professor Loftus agrees that memory works like a recording device.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does percent savings on the y-axis refer to?",
    "answers": [
      "How long it would take for the subject to relearn the new material after some time passes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Listen to the clip that belongs with each question. Then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Clip Play Video The belief held by ancient people that constellations cause seasonal changes on Earth is an example of:",
    "answers": ["An inductive inference"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What point was the speaker illustrating when he mentioned the topic of faith?",
    "answers": [
      "That the stories are what people connect to and attact them to the faith"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 3 Video Clip Play Video Which statement(s) is/are true? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "There is a downward trend of both property and violent crime.",
      "There is a greater decrease of property crime than violent crime."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Question 5 Clip Play Video True or false? Drawing pictures and putting them where you can see them often is one way of studying the lecture information.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s see how effective the notes that you took in the Listening Strategies lecture are. See if they can help you answer the following questions. If not, listen to that lecture again. What is the topic of the lecture?",
    "answers": ["ways to make listening to a lecture easier"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For question 4, listen to the lecture clip below on psychology and take notes as you listen. Pay attention to the information in the charts or graphs. After you listen, use your notes to answer the following question. Question 4 Lecture Clip Play Video What is the reminiscence bump?",
    "answers": [
      "the tendency for older adults to have a higher recollection of early adulthood memories"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "See how well you can determine meaning of an actual professor giving an introduction to Einstein’s General Relativity and Gravitation. The lecture is 4 minutes 39 seconds long. First, watch the entire video, then answer each of the following questions. General Relativity and Gravitation Lecture Play Video How does the professor know many of the students?",
    "answers": ["They took his class before."]
  },
  {
    "question": "After listening to the Note-Taking Practice 3 lecture, use your notes to answer the following questions. Which of the following topics does Dave lecture on?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The purpose of the Research Paragraph is to give specific examples of how the student and the university are a good match.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Approximately 20% of the poster should be white space.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If you manually create a poster by cutting and pasting items, most of the text still needs to be typewritten.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which order should the elements of a powerful conclusion appear?",
    "answers": ["summary, epiphany, thanks, questions "]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you wish to invite the audience to ask questions, which part of the presentation would be a good time to do so?",
    "answers": ["conclusion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the word in this purpose for handouts. To provide an ______ that makes notetaking easier",
    "answers": ["outline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are critical thinking skills? Choose all the apply.",
    "answers": [
      "To give an opinion with appropriate support",
      "To find relationships between different ideas",
      "To see things from different points of view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What level of thinking does the following question represent? “Can you think of any alternatives to producing genetically modified foods that will provide the growing world population with food?”",
    "answers": ["synthesis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? If someone is talking a lot in a discussion and you haven’t said anything, you can interrupt.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Read the following statements from a discussion on whether or not the planet can sustain 9.2 billion people. - “Our earth can sustain 9.2 billion people, but not the way it is currently being managed. We need to do a better job at managing resources, educating people, and sharing wealth.” - “As with technology, there is potential to use our limited resources more efficiently, but we are not doing it.” - “We probably have enough resources to sustain 9.2 billion people; the question is whether or not people can live together or not. With so many people, there may be wars because of differences of opinion.” - “It comes back to if humans can live harmoniously with each other. The more people the more problems there are.” What is the best synthesizing statement for the ideas above?",
    "answers": [
      "The earth has the resources to sustain 9.2 billion people; the threatening issue is whether or not people can live in harmoniously with each other."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "After you watch the two improved videos of the discussion on water scarcity, answer the following questions about David’s academic conversation skills. Which of the following describe David’s physical presence? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "He is on the same level as the rest of the group",
      "He has a clear desk and no distractions in his hand.",
      "He has eye contact with the other members of the group.",
      "He leans into the conversation and uses positive conversational body language, including smiling and nods."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip of the introduction to an academic discussion about poverty. Then answer the question that follows. Play Video The academic collocation “tackle a problem” was used in this video clip. Which of the following best explains this idea?",
    "answers": ["To make a big effort to solve a difficult problem"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The task of a discussion is similar to a blueprint of house because it guides the discussion and focuses the group members.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. The speaker connects with the audience by asking the if they _____________.",
    "answers": ["have a social media account"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If your speech seems too long after rehearsing it, what should you do?",
    "answers": ["Delete some information from the speech"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? To make your evidence stronger, it’s okay to exaggerate research findings.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. While answering questions, seeking confirmation is a good way to ________________.",
    "answers": ["make sure that you have satisfactorily answered a question"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of inflection?",
    "answers": ["to communicate something or keep the audience’s interest"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately what percentage of a poster should contain text?",
    "answers": ["60%"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? It's a good idea to give out handouts at the end of the presentation instead of the beginning.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Complete the sentence. When you want to prepare for an academic discussion, the most important thing to do is ___________________",
    "answers": ["To react to the assigned reading"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You want to mark your text to prepare for a discussion. Which symbol should you use to show an important point to discuss?",
    "answers": ["*"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are considered critical thinking? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": ["analysis", "synthesis", "evaluation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. plausible ______________",
    "answers": ["explanation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why should you use evidence to support a claim when you’re disagreeing with someone?",
    "answers": [
      "It will show that your disagreement is based on logic, not on personal opinion."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of these disagreement phrases, which is the least confrontational?",
    "answers": ["I understand what you’re saying, but . . ."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. contribute ______________",
    "answers": ["significantly", "to the development"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. basic ____________",
    "answers": ["assumption"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. vast _____________",
    "answers": ["range"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an appropriate statement if someone is talking too much?",
    "answers": [
      "“That’s interesting, but we haven’t heard from everyone about this yet.”"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. vary ______________",
    "answers": ["considerably"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What should you do if you have something to say but nobody stops talking?",
    "answers": ["Politely interrupt so you can contribute your idea."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the word that completes the collocation. get ___________",
    "answers": ["involved"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a sentence frame that would precede a statement of synthesis?",
    "answers": ["The next step should be to . . ."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Watch this video clip and then answer the question that follows. Question 1 Video Clip Play Video What is the most important finding?",
    "answers": [
      "The number of violent crime victims has been decreasing since the mid 1990s."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? The kinesthetic learning style is very familiar to people, according to the speaker.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the lecture, what statement would the speaker probably agree with?",
    "answers": [
      "The characteristics of a lecture are more important than the characteristics of a learner when understanding a lecture."
    ]
  }
]
